[Music]
[Música]
What's wrong with me kids, well today I
qué pasa a mí chavalería bueno hoy os
bring you this curious video, I don't know if
traigo este curioso vídeo no sé si
you all know who it is because it was
sabréis todo quién es xq se
decided to pronounce it or transform it or they'll
decidió lo pronunciando o transforma o
call it some other way but the
lo llamarán de alguna otra forma pero el
name in tweets is x q c is a streamer
nombre en tweets es x q c es un streamer
who is always live in tweets
que está en directo siempre en tweets
another from the moment you wake up until you
otra desde que te levantas hasta que te
go to bed we will surely get into
acuestas seguramente nos metamos ahora
tweets right now I'm going to let's
mismo en tweets voy a vamos a
check it out
comprobarlo
we will surely get into tweets right now
seguramente nos metamos ahora mismo en
and live the payment is per month
tweets y en directo el pago al mes
x q if today it is not
x q si hoy no
so direct it is
es tan directo es tan directo
so direct it is so direct it doesn't feel like the
es tan directo no se siente el canal
official channel xq xq
oficial xq xq
what other doesn't know there is no other channel that
qué otro no sabe no hay otro canal de
this is how it is then that is another
que así es este entonces ese es otro
channel that is doing something a
canal que está haciendo algo una
room I don't understand I don't understand
habitación no lo entiendo no lo entiendo
but look here you can see the hours you will see
pero mira aquí podéis ver las horas verá
the hours here ten hours here 19 hours
las horas aquí diez horas aquí 19 horas
here 10 hours or in other words 10 18 hours
aquí 10 horas o sea el 10 18 horas
the guy when he is awake he is
el tío cuando está despierto está el
live literally when he is awake he
directo literal cuando está despierto
is live mother of god
está en directo madre de dios
mother of god I
madre de dios
don't know if this Lara every day or like
no sé si esto lara todos los días o como
recent broadcasts
emisiones recientes
well this one 13 hours ago
bueno este hace 13 horas entendía hace 5
I understood 5 days ago I think it does one day and the next it rests well there are times when you make it continue or I don't know but it's very crazy in flight there's a lot that it does no and then yesterday as you probably know you've probably found out ibai was visiting bikini's house
ibai estuvo de visita en casa de bikini
in agulo and he was good doing his
de agulo y estuvo bueno haciendo su
cameo in both set ups
cameo en los dos set up
and this topic of conversation about
y salido este tema de conversación sobre
x1 came up in a good way you know how
x1 en plan buen rollo tú sabes cómo
they comment on things I don't know
ellos comentan las cosas no sé a cuenta
because I don't know why the name xq came up
de que no sé por qué salió el nombre de
but well the thing is that the
xq pero bueno la cuestión es que el
weather arrived at xq and xq here we have him
clima llegado a xq y xq aquí lo tenemos
reacting he
reaccionando
has
ha
stopped doing 400
dejado hacer 400
and
y
stops doing 400 he
deja de hacer 400
is understanding very well I don't know if he
está entendiendo muy bien no sé si se
is taking seriously not the crazy
está tomando en serio no el proyecto de
crazy project and
loco crazy y
the waves
las olas
the tv everything on the twitter account of
el tv todo en la cuenta de twitter de
the statistics that everyone who everyone
las estadísticas que todo el que todos
already knows which ones no
ya sabe cuáles no
or wins either it's not that I
ni ganas tampoco tampoco
am respect but no not having
es que yo sea respeto pero no no haberse
seen never
visto nunca
heard something of the word respect and
escuchaba algo de la palabra respeto y
that something has liked
eso algo le ha gustado
33 but it is not special incredible
33 pero no es especial increíble
and without credit every day of an average of
y sin crédito cada día de una media de
11  12
11 12
get up
levantarse
like he crashes if it's true the crash is the
como él choca si es verdadera el chocas
same it is the crash I don't know what time it
igual es el choque yo no sé a qué hora
starts I don't know always sara after
empieza no sé siempre sara después de
eating at about what I'm telling you 4
comer a eso de las que te digo yo las 4
maybe it wasn't scheduled they stuck together
a lo mejor no se programó se pegaron
until 5 in the morning the crash came out
hasta las 5 la mañana salió lo del
incredible also the same as this it
chocar increíble también igual que esto
is what was said that it is the same as this is
es lo dicho que es igual que esto sea
this is tremendous
esto es tremendo
what is done
qué se hace
in English the title of the click and vice
en inglés el título del clic y vice
aurum play off a message for well you
aurum play off a mensaje por bueno ya
know no what then over here download
sabéis no lo que luego por aquí bajaur
a play has a message because the
un play tiene un mensaje por xq se
consular
consular
translated it
traducido
is not the same translation it is the same you
no es lo mismo traducción es lo mismo se
have to listen to ibai's tone and the
tiene que escuchar el tono de ibai y el
auto tone not to understand it but
tono de auto no para entenderlo pero
well I don't know if he will understand it very well
bueno no sé si lo va a entender muy bien
and
y
display in me well I don't know if this has been
exhibir en mí bueno no sé si es que esto
translated it is a page that is
se han traducido es una página que se
transcribed directly not to los angeles it
transcribe lo directo no a los ángeles
existed done by in the
existía hecho por en la caja de
comments box and if it is like that or not
comentarios y si es así o no
especially for
en especial para
me
mí
and
y
never
nunca
for additional crashes that he is crazy
para adicional chocas que está loco
too but I imagine it will be because of the
también pero me imagino que será por la
attitude the screams and other
actitud los gritos y demás
einstein I don't know if he has understood it very
einstein no sé si lo ha entendido muy
Well or he didn't mean any bad vibes or
bien o no ha querido mal rollo o lo que
whatever but I think that I think that this is
sea pero yo creo que yo creo que está
a bit of a mess, of course
queda un poco con la cosa claro que
during a change of language the
durante cuenta de un cambio de idioma la
irony the tone of ibai this so ironic
ironía el tono de ibai este tan irónico
and sarcastic and auro places the same
y sarcástico y auro emplace lo mismo a
maybe he doesn't get it but of course he will know he will have assumed
la mejor no la pilla pero claro sabrá
that a colleague and
habrá dado por hecho que un compañero y
colleagues so great because they are not going to be
que compañeros así tan grandes porque no
bad I imagine it is I
van a ir de mala me imagino es me
imagine if you have understood something of what he
imagino si habéis entendido algo de lo
has said put it in the
que ha dicho poner en la caja de
comments box and tell me what you think and
comentarios y decirme qué opina y
family a huge hug
familia un abrazo enorme
[Music]
[Música]